const LegislationFindArticle = [

	{
		questionText: 'Quallification of R.S mps',
		ans: ['A.84'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Office of speaker & Dy speaker',
		ans: ['A.93'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Resolution for Changing subject matters in state list by R.S',
		ans: ['A.249'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Joint Session',
		ans: ['A.108'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'President Vote power is removed in CAAs by which CAA',
		ans: ['24th CAA 1971'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Impeachemnt of president',
		ans: ['A.61'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Veto power od president',
		ans: ['A.111'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Money bill in which Article',
		ans: ['A.110'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Quaram Article',
		ans: ['100(3)'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which A. prohibits courts from proceedings in Parliament and state Leg',
		ans: ['A.121'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Financial bills ',
		ans: ['117(1), 117(3)'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Which CAA removed provision --> 1/3rd can change the Party at once',
		ans: ['91st CAA, 2003'],
	},
	{
		questionText: '10th schedule is added from which CAA',
		ans: ['52nd CAA 1985'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'which CAA removed reservation for 2 anglo Indians in L.S',
		ans: ['104th CAA, 2019'],

	},
	{
		questionText: 'Office of Profit ?',
		ans: ['102(1)(a)'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Anti Defection Law',
		ans: ['102(b)'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'There shall be President , L.S & R.S',
		ans: ['A.79'],
	},
	{
		questionText: 'Special adress by the President',
		ans: ['A.87'],
	},

];

export default LegislationFindArticle;
